Guide to the Fales Portrait/Subject Collection ca. 1800 - 1998 MSS.034
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I
  - Haldane, J.S. Hale, Edward, 1899, Undated (Box 2, Folder 255)
    Includes "Lend a Hand Calendar, 1899" annotated with handwritten statements by Edward Hale
  - Hale, Sarah, Undated (Box 2, Folder 256)
  - Haliburton, Thomas Chandler, Undated (Box 2, Folder 257)
  - Hall, Anna Maria Hall, Donald Hall, Radclyffe, Undated (Box 2, Folder 258)
  - Hallam, Henry, Undated (Box 2, Folder 259)
  - Halleck, Fitz-Greene, Undated (Box 2, Folder 260)
  - Hamilton, Undated (Box 2, Folder 261)
  - Hancock, John Hanley, James Hanson, Lawrence and Elisabeth, Undated (Box 2, Folder 262)
  - Hardwicke, Philip Yorke, 1st Earl of, Undated (Box 2, Folder 263)
  - Hardy, Thomas Hardy, Sir Thomas Masterman, Bart. Harley, John Pritt Harley, George Davies, Undated (Box 2, Folder 264)
  - Harris, Frank Harris, Nellie (Mrs. Frank Harris) (contents removed; see Frank Harris Papers), Undated (Box 2, Folder 265)
  - Harrison, Charles Yale Harrison, Jim, Undated (Box 2, Folder 266)
  - Hastings, Francis Rawdon, "Moira" Hastings, Warren Hawkins, Sir Anthony Hope Hawksbury, Lord, Undated (Box 2, Folder 267)
  - Hawthorne, Julian Hawthorne, Nathaniel, Undated (Box 2, Folder 268)
  - Harris, John Harrison, Constance Harrowby, Dudley Ryder, 2nd Earl of Haydan, B. R. Hayley, William, Undated (Box 2, Folder 269)
  - Hazlitt, William Hazzard, Shirley Heinhold, John M. Hemans, Felicia, Undated (Box 2, Folder 270)
  - Henry, King of England IV, V, VII, VIII, Undated (Box 2, Folder 271)
  - Herkimer, Nicholas Herron, Carolivia Hertford, Francis Charles Seymour-Connay Hewlett, Maurice Hichens, Robert, Undated (Box 2, Folder 272)
  - Higginson, Thomas Wentworth Hijuelos, Oscar Hill, Richard Hill, Thomas Hilliard, Nicholas Hilton, James, Undated (Box 2, Folder 273)
  - Hobart, Alice Tisdale:Hobson, Laura Z. Hofland, Barbara (Wreaks) Hoole Hogarth, William Hogg, James, Undated (Box 3, Folder 274)
  - Holcroft, Thomas Holl, Frank Holland, Josiah Gilbert Holland, Vassal, Baron of Holmes, Oliver Wendall Home, John, Undated (Box 3, Folder 275)
  - Hood, Samuel Hood, 1st Viscount Hood, Thomas, Undated (Box 3, Folder 276)
  - Hook, Theodore Edward Hoppner, John Horne, Richard Henry, Undated (Box 3, Folder 277)
  - Hovédard, don Sylvester Howe, Julia Ward, Undated (Box 3, Folder 278)
  - Howells, William Dean, Undated (Box 3, Folder 279)
  - Howick, Lord Hughes, John Hughes, Thomas Hume, David Humphrey, William Hunt, Leigh Hunter, John (see Cuvier), Undated (Box 3, Folder 280)
  - Hunter, Evan (pseud. Ed McBain), Undated (Box 3, Folder 281)
  - Huntington, William Hurst, Fannie Huskisson, William Huxley, Aldous Huxley, Thomas Henry Ibañez, Vicente Blasco, Undated (Box 3, Folder 282)
  - Ingelow, Jean Irving, Rev. E. Irving, Sir Henry Irving, Washington, Undated (Box 3, Folder 283)
  - Jackson, Daniel Jackson, Helen Maria (Fiske) Hunt Jackson, Holbrook Jacobs, William Wymark Janowitz, Tama, Undated (Box 3, Folder 284)
  - James I, King of Scotland James, Henry Jameson, Anna Brownell Jameson, George, Undated (Box 3, Folder 285)
  - Janin, Jules Gabriel Jeans, Sir James Jeffers, Robinson Jefferson, Joseph, Undated (Box 3, Folder 286)
  - Jerrold, Douglas William, Undated (Box 3, Folder 287)
  - Jeffrey, Francis, Lord Jerdan, William Jerningham, Edward Jerome, Jerome Klapka Jones, Henry Adkins, Undated (Box 3, Folder 288)
  - Johnson, James Weldon Johnson, Samuel Jones, James Jong, Erica, Undated (Box 3, Folder 289)
  - Joyce, James, Undated (Box 3, Folder 290)
  - Kane, E.K., Undated (Box 3, Folder 291)
  - Kaprow, Allan, Undated (Box 3, Folder 292)
    Holds posters, pamphlets, and mailers advertising Kaprow's activities
  - Karl, Waldo, Undated (Box 3, Folder 293)
  - Keats, John, Undated (Box 3, Folder 294)
  - Keller, Helen, Undated (Box 3, Folder 295)
  - Kemble, Charles, Undated (Box 3, Folder 296)
  - Kent and Strathern, Edward Augustus, Duke of, Undated (Box 3, Folder 297)
  - Kent, Rockwell, Undated (Box 3, Folder 298)
  - Kent, Victoria Mary Louisa, Duchess of, Undated (Box 3, Folder 299)
  - Kernahan, Coulson Kerouac, Jack, Undated (Box 3, Folder 300)
  - Ketel, Cornelius, Undated (Box 3, Folder 301)
  - Kipling, Rudyard, Undated (Box 3, Folder 302)
  - Kingsley, Charles, Undated (Box 3, Folder 303)
  - Kneller, Sir Godfrey, Bart., Undated (Box 3, Folder 304)
  - Knighton, Sir William, Bart., Undated (Box 3, Folder 305)
  - Knowles, James Sheridon Komroff, Manuel Kotzwinkle, William Kreymborg, Alfred Kumin, Maxine, Undated (Box 3, Folder 306)
  - LaBruyère, Jean de, Undated (Box 3, Folder 307)
  - Lackington, James, Undated (Box 3, Folder 308)
  - Lafayette, Marie Joseph Paul, Undated (Box 3, Folder 309)
  - Laighton, Oscar, Undated (Box 3, Folder 310)
  - Lamartine, M. Lamb, Caroline, Lady, Undated (Box 3, Folder 311)
  - Lamb, Charles, Undated (Box 3, Folder 312)
  - Lambert, George, Undated (Box 3, Folder 313)
  - Landon, Letitia Elizabeth, Undated (Box 3, Folder 314)
  - Landseer, Thomas, Undated (Box 3, Folder 315)
  - Lang, Matheson, Undated (Box 3, Folder 316)
  - Lanier, Nicholas, Undated (Box 3, Folder 317)
  - Lansdowne, Henry Petty Fitzmaurice, 3rd Marquis of, Undated (Box 3, Folder 318)
  - Larcom, Lucy Lardner, Ring, Undated (Box 3, Folder 319)
  - Laud, William, Archbishop of Canterbury, Undated (Box 3, Folder 320)
  - Lawrence, D.H., Undated (Box 3, Folder 321)
  - Leacock, Stephen LeBrun, Charles, Undated (Box 3, Folder 322)
  - LeGallienne, Richard Leicester, Thomas William Coke, 1st Earl of Leonard, Elmore, Undated (Box 3, Folder 323)
  - Lely, Sir Peter, Undated (Box 3, Folder 324)
  - Lemon, Mark LeQueure, William Lessing, Doris, Undated (Box 3, Folder 325)
  - LeSeur, Undated (Box 3, Folder 326)
  - L'Estrange, Sir Roger, Undated (Box 3, Folder 327)
  - Lever, Charles Levin, Ira Lewis, Flora, Undated (Box 3, Folder 328)
  - Lightfoot, John Linton, Mrs. Lynn, Undated (Box 3, Folder 329)
  - Liverpool, Charles Jenkinson, 1st Earl of Liverpool, Robert Banks Jenkinson, Earl of, Undated (Box 3, Folder 330)
  - Locke, William John Lockhart, John Gibson, Undated (Box 3, Folder 331)
  - Lombart, Pierre, Undated (Box 3, Folder 332)
  - London, England, Undated (Box 3, Folder 332-A)
  - London, Jack, Undated (Box 3, Folder 333)
  - Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth, Undated (Box 3, Folder 334)
  - Loos, Anita Lorraine, Claude, Undated (Box 3, Folder 335)
  - Lossing, Benson John, Undated (Box 3, Folder 336)
  - Louis XIII, King of France, Undated (Box 3, Folder 337)
  - Louis XIV, King of France, Undated (Box 3, Folder 338)
  - Louis XVIII, King of France, Undated (Box 3, Folder 339)
  - Lowe, Sir Hudson, Undated (Box 3, Folder 340)
  - Lowell, James Russell Lowell, Percival, Undated (Box 3, Folder 341)
  - Lucullus, L. Licinius Luicoler (?), Joseph C, Undated (Box 3, Folder 342)
  - Lydgate, John, Undated (Box 3, Folder 343)
  - Lyell, Sir Charles, Undated (Box 3, Folder 344)
  - Lytton, Edward George Earle Lytton Bulwer, 1st Baron, Undated (Box 3, Folder 345)
  - Lytton, Robert J., Undated (Box 3, Folder 346)
  - McCarthy, Cormac McCarthy, May Macaulay, Thomas Babington, Undated (Box 3, Folder 347)
  - McCord, Howard, Undated (Box 3, Folder 348)
    Contents consist of one handwritten poem
  - MacDonald, John D. Macdonough, Thomas, Undated (Box 3, Folder 349)
  - Machen, Arthur McGahern, John McGuane, Thomas, Undated (Box 3, Folder 350)
  - McKenna, Stephen, Undated (Box 3, Folder 351)
  - MacKenzie, Henry Mackintosh, Sir James MacLeish, Archibald Maclise, Daniel McMillan, Terry, Undated (Box 3, Folder 352)
  - Madden, David Malamud, Bernard Malanga, Gerard, Undated (Box 3, Folder 353)
  - Malone, Edmund, Undated (Box 3, Folder 354)
  - Mallarmé, Stephane Manet, Madame, Undated (Box 3, Folder 355)
  - Mansfield, Lord, Undated (Box 3, Folder 356)
  - Markham, Edwin, Undated (Box 3, Folder 357)
  - Marlborough, Duke of, Undated (Box 3, Folder 358)
  - Marquand, John P., Undated (Box 3, Folder 359)
  - Marquis, Don Martineau, Harriet, Undated (Box 3, Folder 360)
  - Masefield, John, Undated (Box 3, Folder 361)
  - Mason, A.E.W., Undated (Box 3, Folder 362)
  - Mason, Bobbie Ann, Undated (Box 3, Folder 363)
  - Mathews, Lucia Elizabeth, Undated (Box 3, Folder 364)
  - Maugham, William Somerset, Undated (Box 3, Folder 365)
  - Mawbey, Sir Joseph, Bart., Undated (Box 3, Folder 366)
  - Maytag, Ken, Undated (Box 3, Folder 367)
  - Mead, Richard, Undated (Box 3, Folder 368)
  - Mécène, Undated (Box 3, Folder 369)
  - Medici, Catherine de Melbourne, William Lamb, Baron of, Undated (Box 3, Folder 370)
  - Melville, Henry Dundas, 1st Viscount, Undated (Box 3, Folder 371)
  - Melville, Herman Melville, Robert Saunders, 2nd Viscount, Undated (Box 3, Folder 372)
  - Meredith, George, Undated (Box 3, Folder 373)
  - Mercier, Philip, Undated (Box 3, Folder 374)
  - Merry, Robert Merton, Thomas, Undated (Box 3, Folder 375)
  - Michener, James A. Millais, Sir John Everett, Undated (Box 3, Folder 376)
  - Millay, Edna St. Vincent, Undated (Box 3, Folder 377)
  - Miller, Arthur Miller, Joaquin Milne, A.A., Undated (Box 3, Folder 378)
  - Milton, Lord Andrew Fletcher, Undated (Box 3, Folder 379)
  - Miscellaneous/Unidentified Portraits, Undated (Box 3, Folder 379-A)
  - Mitchell, Donald Grant Mitchell, Margaret, Undated (Box 3, Folder 380)
  - Mitchell, Silas Weir, Undated (Box 3, Folder 381)
  - Mitford, Mary Russell, Undated (Box 3, Folder 382)
  - Molière, Jean Baptiste Poquelin, Undated (Box 3, Folder 383)
  - Molloy, Undated (Box 3, Folder 384)
  - Monamy, Peter Monette, Paul Monroe, Mary, Undated (Box 3, Folder 385)
  - Montagu, Mrs., Undated (Box 3, Folder 386)
  - Montague, Lady Mary Wortley, Undated (Box 3, Folder 387)
  - Monteagle, Thomas Spring-Rice, Baron, Undated (Box 3, Folder 388)
  - Count Montfort, John IV, and his wife Joanna of Flanders, Undated (Box 3, Folder 388-A)
  - Montrose, James Graham, 4th Duke of, Undated (Box 3, Folder 389)
  - Moore, Thomas, Undated (Box 3, Folder 390)
  - Moore, Augustus Moore, George Moore, Sir John Moore, Marianne More, Sir Antonio, Undated (Box 3, Folder 391)
  - More, Hannah, Undated (Box 3, Folder 392)
  - More, Sir Thomas, Undated (Box 3, Folder 393)
  - Morell, Thomas, Undated (Box 3, Folder 394)
  - Morgan, Daniel, Undated (Box 3, Folder 395)
  - Morgan, Sydney (Owenson), Lady, Undated (Box 3, Folder 396)
  - Morghen, Raphael, Undated (Box 3, Folder 397)
  - Morland, G., Undated (Box 3, Folder 398)
  - Morley, Christopher, Undated (Box 3, Folder 399)
  - Morris, George Pope, Undated (Box 3, Folder 400)
  - Morris, William Morrow, Dwight M., Undated (Box 3, Folder 401)
  - Morse, Samuel Finley Breeze, Undated (Box 3, Folder 402)
  - Motherwell, William, Undated (Box 3, Folder 403)
  - Motley, John Lathrop, Undated (Box 3, Folder 404)
  - Moulton, Mrs. Louise (Chandler), Undated (Box 3, Folder 405)
  - Moultrie, William, Undated (Box 3, Folder 406)
  - Mount, William Sydney, Undated (Box 3, Folder 407)
  - Mowatt, Anna Cora, Undated (Box 3, Folder 408)
  - Mulready, William, Undated (Box 3, Folder 409)
  - Murfree, Mary Noailles, Undated (Box 3, Folder 410)
  - Murillo, Bartolomé Esteban, Undated (Box 3, Folder 411)
  - Murray, David Christie, Undated (Box 3, Folder 412)
    Only a photocopy of a short newspaper article.
  - Murray, Lindley, Undated (Box 4, Folder 413)
  - Murray, Thomas, Undated (Box 4, Folder 414)
  - Mytens, Daniel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 415)
  - Napolean I, Emperor of France, Undated (Box 4, Folder 416)
  - Napolean III, Emperor of France, Undated (Box 4, Folder 417)
  - Nast, Thomas, Undated (Box 4, Folder 418)
  - Neal, John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 419)
  - Nelson, Horatio, Viscount, Undated (Box 4, Folder 420)
  - Nero, Emperor of Rome, Undated (Box 4, Folder 421)
  - New York City, Undated (Box 4, Folder 422)
  - New York Society Library, Undated (Box 4, Folder 423)
  - Newman, John Henry, Cardinal, Undated (Box 4, Folder 424)
  - Nichols, John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 425)
  - Nicholson, Meredith Nin, Anaïs, Undated (Box 4, Folder 426)
  - Norris, Kathleen, Undated (Box 4, Folder 427)
  - North, Lord, Undated (Box 4, Folder 428)
  - Northcote, James, Undated (Box 4, Folder 429)
  - Norton, Caroline (Sheridan), Undated (Box 4, Folder 430)
  - Norton, Charles Eliot, Undated (Box 4, Folder 431)
  - Noyes, Alfred, Undated (Box 4, Folder 432)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol O'Casey, Sean, Undated (Box 4, Folder 433)
  - Ochs, Richard Odets, Clifford, Undated (Box 4, Folder 434)
  - O'Flaherty, Liam O'Hara, Frank, Undated (Box 4, Folder 435)
  - Oliphant, Mrs. O.W., Undated (Box 4, Folder 436)
  - Oliver, Isaac Oliver, Peter, Undated (Box 4, Folder 437)
  - Opie, Mrs. Amelia (Alderson) Opie, John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 438)
  - Oppenheimer, Ernest Kant Oppenheimer, Joel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 439)
  - Orczy, Emmuskz, Baroness, Undated (Box 4, Folder 440)
  - "Organ Grinder", Undated (Box 4, Folder 441)
  - Owens, Rochelle Oxford, Robert Harley, 1st Earl of, Undated (Box 4, Folder 442)
  - Page, Anne Page, T. Nelson Paine, Thomas, Undated (Box 4, Folder 443)
  - Palmerston, Henry John Temple, 3rd Viscount, Undated (Box 4, Folder 444)
  - Panter-Downes, Mollie, Undated (Box 4, Folder 445)
  - Pardoe, Julia Paris, Undated (Box 4, Folder 446)
  - Parker, Gilbert, Undated (Box 4, Folder 447)
  - Pass, Simon, Undated (Box 4, Folder 448)
  - Pater, Walter, Undated (Box 4, Folder 449)
  - Payn, James, Undated (Box 4, Folder 450)
  - Payne, J. [John?], Undated (Box 4, Folder 451)
  - Payne, John Howard, Undated (Box 4, Folder 452)
  - Peel, Sir Robert, Bart., Undated (Box 4, Folder 453)
  - Pennell, Joseph, Undated (Box 4, Folder 454)
  - Pen, Undated (Box 4, Folder 455)
  - Perceval, Spencer, Undated (Box 4, Folder 456)
  - Percival, James Gates, Undated (Box 4, Folder 457)
  - Perry, James Perry, Richard Peter The Great, Undated (Box 4, Folder 458)
  - Peto, Sir Samuel Morton, Bart., Undated (Box 4, Folder 459)
  - Phelps, William Leonard, Undated (Box 4, Folder 460)
  - Phillpots, Eden, Undated (Box 4, Folder 460-A)
  - Piercy, Marge Pierpont, John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 461)
  - Pignotti, Lamberto, Undated (Box 4, Folder 462)
  - Pine, John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 463)
  - Pinero, Sir John Wing, Undated (Box 4, Folder 464)
  - Pinkerton, John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 465)
  - Pinkey, William Pinter, Harold, Undated (Box 4, Folder 466)
  - Pitt, William, Undated (Box 4, Folder 467)
  - See Oversize, Folder 1 Plan of the City of New York (1797) Plan of the City of New York (1807), Undated (Box 4, Folder 467-A)
  - Plante, David Platoff, Hetman, Undated (Box 4, Folder 468)
  - Poetry, Undated (Box 4, Folder 469)
    Includes advertiesments in the form of posters and direct mail for a variety of poetry publications and events, such as the Poets Press
  - Pole, Sir Charles Morice, Undated (Box 4, Folder 470)
  - Polenberg, Cornelius, Undated (Box 4, Folder 471)
  - Pollock, Sir Jonathan Frederick, Bart., Undated (Box 4, Folder 472)
  - Pope, Alexander, Undated (Box 4, Folder 473)
  - Porson, Richard Porter, Connie, Undated (Box 4, Folder 474)
  - Porter, Fairfield, Undated (Box 4, Folder 475)
  - Porter, Jane, Undated (Box 4, Folder 476)
  - Potok, Chaim Poussin, Nicolas Powell, Padgett, Undated (Box 4, Folder 477)
  - Poynter, Edmund, Undated (Box 4, Folder 478)
  - Pratt, Samuel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 479)
  - Prentice, George Denison, Undated (Box 4, Folder 480)
  - Prescott, William H., Undated (Box 4, Folder 481)
  - Price, Reynolds Price, Richard Priestly, Joseph, Undated (Box 4, Folder 482)
  - Printing (Miscellaneous Leaves), Undated (Box 4, Folder 483)
  - Printing (Fine Press), Undated (Box 4, Folder 483-A)
    Includes pamphlets and letters from Thornwillow Press as well as advertisements, and a catalog regarding exhibitions of Wendy Marks' art
  - Pritchard, Hannah (Vaughan) Pritchett, V.S., Undated (Box 4, Folder 484)
  - Procter, Adelaide, Undated (Box 4, Folder 485)
  - Procter, Brian, Undated (Box 4, Folder 486)
  - Putnam, H. Phelps Puzo, Mario, Undated (Box 4, Folder 487)
  - Queensbury, William Douglas, 4th Duke of, Undated (Box 4, Folder 488)
  - Quintus, Horatius Flaccus, Undated (Box 4, Folder 489)
  - Rachel, Madame Raeburn, Sir Henry, Undated (Box 4, Folder 490)
  - Raglan, Fitzroy James Henry Somerset, Baron, Undated (Box 4, Folder 491)
  - Raine, William MacLeod, Undated (Box 4, Folder 492)
  - Raleigh, Sir Walter Ransom, John Crowe, Undated (Box 4, Folder 493)
  - Read, Piers Paul Read, T.B. Reed, Ishmael, Undated (Box 4, Folder 494)
  - Reeve, John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 495)
  - Reid, Mayne, Undated (Box 4, Folder 496)
  - [Empty], Undated (Box 4, Folder 497)
  - Rembrandt (w/ Sir David Wilkie), Undated (Box 4, Folder 498)
  - Reynolds, Sir Joshua, Undated (Box 4, Folder 499)
  - Rich, Adrienne, Undated (Box 4, Folder 500)
  - Richardson, Henry Handel (pseud. for Ethel Florence Lindsay Robertson), Undated (Box 4, Folder 501)
  - Richmond, Charles Lennox, Duke of, Undated (Box 4, Folder 502)
  - Richmond, Frances Teresa, Duchess of, Undated (Box 4, Folder 503)
  - Riley, James Whitcomb Riley, John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 504)
  - Rinehart, Mary Robert, Undated (Box 4, Folder 505)
  - Ripley, Sarah Bradford Ritchie, Anne Isabella (Thackeray), Undated (Box 4, Folder 506)
  - Ritson, Joseph, Undated (Box 4, Folder 507)
  - Rivera, Diego, Undated (Box 4, Folder 508)
  - Robertson, William Robinson, Edwin Arlington, Undated (Box 4, Folder 509)
  - Robinson, Henry Crabb, Undated (Box 4, Folder 510)
  - Rockingham, Charles, Marquis of, Undated (Box 4, Folder 511)
  - Roestraten, Undated (Box 4, Folder 512)
  - Rogers, Samuel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 513)
  - Roiphe, Anne Rogers, Will, Undated (Box 4, Folder 514)
  - Romilly, Sir Samuel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 515)
  - Rosbery, Archibald John Primrose, 4th Earl of Roscoe, William, Undated (Box 4, Folder 516)
  - Rosetti, Dante Gabriel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 517)
  - Rossini, Gioacchino Antonio, Undated (Box 4, Folder 518)
  - Rothenberg, Jerome, Undated (Box 4, Folder 519)
  - Roubillac, Louis François, Undated (Box 4, Folder 520)
  - Rousseau, Jean Jacques, Undated (Box 4, Folder 521)
  - Rowan, Louis, Undated (Box 4, Folder 522)
  - Rowlandson, Thomas Roxburgh, John Ker, 3rd Duke of Royston, Arthur, Undated (Box 4, Folder 523)
  - Rubens, Undated (Box 4, Folder 524)
  - Rukeyser, Muriel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 525)
  - Ruskin, John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 526)
  - Russell, Lord John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 527)
  - Ryder, Thomas, Undated (Box 4, Folder 528)
  - Rysbrack, John Michael, Undated (Box 4, Folder 529)
  - Sacheverell, Henry, Undated (Box 4, Folder 530)
  - Sackville West, Vita, Undated (Box 4, Folder 531)
  - St. Ledger, Undated (Box 4, Folder 532)
  - Saint-Pierre, J.H. Bernardin, Undated (Box 4, Folder 533)
  - St. Vincent, John Jerris, Earl of, Undated (Box 4, Folder 534)
  - Sala, George Augustus, Undated (Box 4, Folder 535)
  - Sale, Major General Sir Robert H., Undated (Box 4, Folder 536)
  - Salisbury, Marchioness of, Undated (Box 4, Folder 537)
  - Saltus, Edgar Evertson, Undated (Box 4, Folder 538)
  - Sandburg, Carl, Undated (Box 4, Folder 539)
  - Sanders, Ed, Undated (Box 4, Folder 540)
  - Saunderson, Robert, Undated (Box 4, Folder 541)
  - Sargent, Epes, Undated (Box 4, Folder 542)
  - Sarton, May, Undated (Box 4, Folder 543)
  - Saumarez, Sir J., Undated (Box 4, Folder 544)
  - Saroyan, William, Undated (Box 4, Folder 545)
  - Savory, Teo, Undated (Box 4, Folder 546)
  - Saxe, John Godfrey, Undated (Box 4, Folder 547)
  - Saxe-Coberg, Prince Leopold, Undated (Box 4, Folder 548)
  - Schiavonetti, Luigi (or Schiavonetti, Niccolò), Undated (Box 4, Folder 549)
  - Schiller Schinto, Jeanne, Undated (Box 4, Folder 550)
  - Schorerer, Mark Schlegel, August Wilhelm von, Undated (Box 4, Folder 551)
  - Schreiner, Olive, Undated (Box 4, Folder 552)
  - Schuyler, James Schuyler, Philip John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 553)
  - Scott, John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 554)
  - Scott, Sir Walter, Bart., Undated (Box 4, Folder 555)
  - Sedgwick, Ann Douglas, Undated (Box 4, Folder 556)
  - Sedgwick, Catharine Maria, Undated (Box 4, Folder 557)
  - See, Carolyn See, Richard Henry Seelye, John Seeman, Elizabeth, Undated (Box 4, Folder 558)
  - Selden, John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 559)
  - Servire Press, Undated (Box 4, Folder 560)
  - Sewell, Samuel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 561)
  - Seymour, Michael, Undated (Box 4, Folder 562)
  - Shaftesbury, Cropley Ashley-Cooper, Earl of, Undated (Box 4, Folder 563)
  - Shakespeare, Undated (Box 4, Folder 564)
  - Sharp, William, Undated (Box 4, Folder 565)
  - Shaw, Sir James, Undated (Box 4, Folder 566)
  - Shaw, George Bernard, Undated (Box 4, Folder 567)
  - Shelley, Percy Bysshe, Undated (Box 4, Folder 568)
  - Sheridan, Arthur Brinsley, Undated (Box 4, Folder 569)
  - Shields, David, Undated (Box 4, Folder 570)
  - Shillaber, Benjamin Penhallow Shreve, Susan Richards, Undated (Box 4, Folder 571)
  - Sidmouth, Lord, Undated (Box 4, Folder 572)
  - Siddons, Mary F. Scott, Undated (Box 4, Folder 573)
  - Sigourney, [Lydia] [Howard] (Huntley), Undated (Box 4, Folder 574)
  - Simic, Charles, Undated (Box 4, Folder 575)
  - Sinclair, Upton Sissman, L.E. Skeat, Walter William, Undated (Box 4, Folder 576)
  - Sladen, Douglas Brooke Wheelton, Undated (Box 4, Folder 577)
  - Sloane, Sir Hans, Bart. Smeaton, John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 578)
  - Smirke, Robert, Undated (Box 4, Folder 579)
  - Smith, Albert Richard, Undated (Box 4, Folder 580)
  - Smith, Francis Hopkinson, Undated (Box 4, Folder 581)
  - Smith, J.H., Undated (Box 4, Folder 582)
  - Smith, Mrs. Charlotte (Turner), Undated (Box 4, Folder 583)
  - Smith, Sir William Sidney, Undated (Box 4, Folder 584)
  - Smith, Seba, Undated (Box 4, Folder 585)
  - Smith, Sydney, Undated (Box 4, Folder 586)
  - "Smokey the Bear Sutra", Undated (Box 4, Folder 587)
  - Snodgrass, Gabriel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 588)
  - Social Protest 1960's ("Yippie"), Undated (Box 4, Folder 589)
  - Somerville, Mary Fairfax, Undated (Box 4, Folder 590)
  - Sontag, Mademoiselle, Undated (Box 4, Folder 591)
  - Southey, Miss, Undated (Box 4, Folder 592)
  - Southey, Robert, Undated (Box 4, Folder 593)
  - Spencer, George John Spencer, 2nd Earl of Spark, Muriel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 594)
  - Spencer, Herbert, Undated (Box 4, Folder 595)
  - Spender, Stephen, Undated (Box 4, Folder 596)
  - Staël, Madame de, Undated (Box 4, Folder 597)
  - Stafford, Granville Leveson-Gower, 1st Marquis of, Undated (Box 4, Folder 598)
  - Stanley, Lord, Undated (Box 4, Folder 599)
  - Stannard, Henrietta Eliza Vaughan (Palmer) (pseud. John Strange Winter), Undated (Box 4, Folder 600)
  - Starrett, Vincent, Undated (Box 4, Folder 601)
  - Stedman, Edmund Clarence, Undated (Box 5, Folder 602)
  - Steele, Sir Richard, Undated (Box 5, Folder 603)
  - Stein, Gertrude, Undated (Box 5, Folder 604)
  - Steinbeck, John, Undated (Box 5, Folder 605)
  - Stephen, Sir Leslie, Undated (Box 5, Folder 606)
  - Stephens, James, Undated (Box 5, Folder 607)
  - Stephens, Michael, Undated (Box 5, Folder 608)
  - Stephenson, George, Undated (Box 5, Folder 609)
  - Stevens, George Alexander, Undated (Box 5, Folder 609-A)
  - Stockton, Frank Richard, Undated (Box 5, Folder 610)
  - Stone, Robert, Undated (Box 5, Folder 611)
  - Stoker, Bram Storck, John, Undated (Box 5, Folder 612)
  - Strange, Sir Robert, Undated (Box 5, Folder 613)
  - Strickland, Agnes, Undated (Box 5, Folder 614)
  - Strachey, Lytton Styron, William, Undated (Box 5, Folder 615)
  - Sumner, Charles, Undated (Box 5, Folder 616)
  - Sussex, Augustus Frederick, Duke of, Undated (Box 5, Folder 617)
  - Svelton, George, Undated (Box 5, Folder 618)
  - Swift, Jonathan, Undated (Box 5, Folder 619)
  - Swinburne, Algernon Charles, Undated (Box 5, Folder 620)
  - Tabley, Georgiana Maria (Cottin), Lady de, Undated (Box 5, Folder 621)